Guide to the Brown University Portraits 1857-2015
Brown University Library
Brown University Portraits
1857-2015
OF-1V-1
John Hay Library University Archives and Manuscripts Box A Brown University Providence, RI, 02912 Telephone: Manuscripts: 401-863-3723; University Archives: 401-863-2148 Email: Manuscripts: hay@brown.edu; University Archives: archives@brown.edu
3.75 linear feet
Brown University
The Brown University Portraits files contain general files, committee reports, correspondence, artist information, copies of portraits, portrait locations, and other documents related to Brown University's portrait collection. The files date from 1857 to 2015, with a bulk of the materials undated but from the twentieth century.
Biographical/Historical Note
The University's Portrait Collection dates to 1815, the year Brown acquired its first portrait — a painting of its founding president James Manning. As the collection has grown over the years the subjects of these portraits have included administrators, faculty, students, trustees, and benefactors. Many are Brown graduates, although some are community leaders, military heroes, or other figures with only tangential connection to the University but still thought worthy of emulation. Most of the people portrayed in these images lived lives that in some way benefited Brown, and consequentially have been meant to serve as an inspiration.
Collection information
The Brown University Portraits files contain general files, committee reports, correspondence, artist information, copies of portraits, portrait locations, and other documents related to Brown University's portrait collection. The files date from 1857 to 2015, with a bulk of the materials undated but from the twentieth century.
There are no restrictions on access, except that the collection can only be seen by prior appointment. Some materials may be stored off-site and cannot be produced on the same day on which they are requested.
Series 1. General files
Series 2. Correspondence
Series 3. W.C. Poland Notes
Series 4. Artist Information
Series 5. Subjects
- General files, 1857-1992; Series 1
  - Locations, 1904-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Locations, 1907-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Locations, [undated] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Location - Changes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Location - Annmary Brown Memorial, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Location - Sayles Hall, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Location - Sayles Hall, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Location - John Hay Library, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Location - Pembroke Hall, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Location - Rockefeller Library, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Location - Rhode Island, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Location - Unlocated, [undated] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Location - Missing, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Labels, [undated] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Catalogues, 1948-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Loans, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Valuations, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Restoration, 1944-1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1857 Gift (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Prints, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Paintings, Prints, Etchings, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brown Portraits, [undated] (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - (Portrait Sketches), 1947-1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Portrait Cards, [undated] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee on University Portraits - Report to the A&E Committee, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committee on University Portraits - Survey, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Work in Progress, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - (Research on Early Portraits), 1967-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (Offered Subject to Prior Sale), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1944-1989; Series 2
  - 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1952-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - [Correspondence], 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Correspondence], 1966-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- W.C. Poland Notes, 1909-1963; Series 3
  - Acquisition of Portraits, 1909-1911 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cataloguing of Portraits, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Commissions Awarded, 1901-1911 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Labels, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans R-8, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Coney, Samuel (Unlocated), [undated] (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Carmichael, Leonar R-15, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cox, Samuel Sullivan R-12, [undated] (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Tefft, Thomas Alexander, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - General, 1912-1916 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Rhode Island Hall, [undated] (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Artist Information, 1896-1967; Series 4
  - Alexander, Cosmo, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Amans, Jacques, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arnold, John Nelson, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Charles W., 1909 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chapin, Marie Louise, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Diranian, Sarkis, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Durin, Alfred Paul, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Flagg, Jared Bradley, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gaspars, John Baptist, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Grundman, Otto, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Harding, Chester, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1904-1916 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Healey, George Peter Alexander, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Herkomer, Hubert (Von), 1909 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hinckley, Robert, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Huntington, Daniel, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ingham, Charles Cromwell, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Irwin, Benoni, 1896-1909 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Jackson, Charles Ackerman, 1911-1919 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - King, Charles Beard, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Lazarus, Jacob H., 1911 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Lincoln, James Sullivan, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Oertel, Johannes Adam, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Perry, Oliver Hazard, [undated] (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Pratt, Henry Cheeves, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Selinger, Jean Paul, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Stuart, Jane, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Walker, John Henson, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Yewell, George H., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Subjects, 1857-2015; Series 5
  - BP1: Manning, James, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - BP2: Brown, Nicholas, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - BP3: Manning, James, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - BP4: Wayland, Francis, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - BP5: Judson, Adoniram, 1968-2008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - BP6: Coddington, Wm. Jr., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - BP7: Brown, Moses, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - BP8: Barton, William, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - BP9: Stuart, Gilbert, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - BP10: Slater, Samuel, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - BP11: Ives, Thomas Poynton, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - BP12: Burges, Tristam, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - BP13: Wheaton, Henry, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - BP14: Perry, Oliver Hazard, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - BP15: Robbins, Asher, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - BP16: Berkeley, George, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - BP17: Channing, Wm. Ellery, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - BP18: Crocker, Nathan Bourne, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - BP19: Rodman, Isaac Pearce, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - BP20: Greene, Christopher, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - BP21: Drowne, Solomon, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - BP22:Charles II (King of England), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - BP23: Catherine of Braganza, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - BP24: Rogers, William, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - BP25: Wheaton, Levi, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - BP26: Cromwell, Oliver, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - BP27: Jackson, Andrew, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - BP28: Pitman, John, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - BP29: Varnum, James Mitchell, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - BP30: Sears, Barnas, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - BP31: Blanding, William, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - BP32: Brown, William Ide, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - BP33: Bridgham, Samuel Willard, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - BP34: Carter, Benj. Bowen, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - BP35: Douville, Pierre, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - BP36: Parsons, Usher (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - BP37: Caswell, Alexis, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - BP38: Clifford, John Henry, 1909-1911 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - BP39: Francis, John Brown, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - BP40: Hazard, Rowland Gibson, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - BP41: Metcalf, Theron, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - BP42: Davis, Isaac, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - BP43: Elton, Romeo, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - BP44: Duncan, Alexander, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - BP45: Slater, Horatio Nelson, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - BP46: Diman, Jeremiah Lewis, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - BP47: Jackson, Richard, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - BP48: Brown, James, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - BP49: Chace, George Ide, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - BP50: Lincoln, John Larkin, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - BP51: Howell, David, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - BP52: Dyer, Elisha, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - BP53: Fobes, Perez, 1965-2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - BP54: Gammell, William, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - BP55: Rovinson, Ezekiel Gilman, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - BP56: Doyle, Thomas Arthur, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - BP57: Greene, Samuel Stillman, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - BP58: Manning, Margaret Stites (Mrs. James Manning), [undated] (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - BP59: Arnold, Samuel Greene, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - BP60: Caldwell, Samuel Lunt, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - BP61: Messer, Asa, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - BP62: Sayles, William Clarke, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - BP63: Sayles, William Francis, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - BP64: Dunn, Rovinson Potter, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - BP65: Foster, Lafayette Sabine, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - BP66: Woods, Alva, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - BP67: Jenks, John Whipple Potter, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - BP68: Angell, James Burrill, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - BP69: Arnold, Peleg, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - BP70: Coggeshall, Josias Haydon, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - BP71: Goddard, William Giles, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - BP72: Greene, Nathanael, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - BP73: Greene, Nathanael, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - BP74: Banigan, Joseph, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - BP75: Blake, Eli Whitney, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - BP76: Peirce, John, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - BP77: Bartlett, John Russell, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - BP78: Allen, Zachariah, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - BP79: Guild, Reuben Aldredge, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - BP80: Bancroft, Timothy Whiting, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - BP81: Williams, Alonzo, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - BP82: Andrews, Elisha Benjamin, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - BP83: Goddard, William, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - BP84: Brown, Moses, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - BP85: Brown, Nicholas, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - BP86: Brown, Nicholas, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - BP87: Brown, Caroline Clements, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - BP88: Brown, Annmary, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - BP89: Hawkins, Annmary Brown, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - BP90: Hawkins, Annmary Brown, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - BP91: Hawkins, Rush Christopher, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - BP92: Trumbull, John, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - BP93: Greene, Albert Gorton, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - BP94: Wilson, George Francis, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - BP95: Clarke, Benjamin Franklin, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - BP96: Harkness, Albert, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - BP97: Hawkins, Rush Christopher, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - BP98: Burgess, Thomas, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - BP99: Granger, Daniel Larned Davis, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - BP100: Lamont, Hammond, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - BP101: Hay, John, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - BP102: Whitman, Sarah Helen, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - BP103: Bradley, Charles Smith, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - BP104: DeWolf, James Andrews, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - BP105: Thayer, Eli, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - BP106: Church, George Earl, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - BP107: Lyman, Daniel Wanton, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - BP108: King, Lida Shaw, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - BP109: Allinson, Anne Crosby Emery, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - BP110: Doyle, Sarah Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - BP111: Appleton, John Howard, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - BP112: Monroe, John Albert, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - BP113: Woods, Marshall, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - BP114: Olney, Stephen Thayer, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - BP115: Hughes, Charles Evans, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - BP116: Peck, Allen Ormsbee, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - BP117: Faunce, William Herbert Perry, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - BP118: Chace, Arnold Buffum, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - BP119: Langdon, Courtney, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - BP120: Keen, William Williams, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - BP121: Marcy, William Learned, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - BP122: Bumpus, Hermon Carey, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - BP123: Bronson, Walter Cochrane, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - BP124: Littlefield, George Leander, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - BP125: Eastman, Samuel Coffin, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - BP126: Randall, Otis Everett, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - BP127: Allinson, Francis Greenleaf, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - BP128: Harkness, Albert Granger, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - BP129: Wayland, Francis, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - BP130: Chace, Arnold Buffum, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - BP131: Greene, John Francis, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - BP132: Woods, John Carter Brown, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - BP133: Burleigh, George Shepard, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - BP134: Howe, Samuel Gridley, 1976-2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - BP135: Carnegie, Andrew, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - BP136: Carnegie, Andrew, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - BP137: Andrews, Elisha Benjamin, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - BP138: Mead, Albert Davis, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - BP139: Everett, Walter Goodnow, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - BP140: Poland, William Carey, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - BP141: Bumpus, Hermon Carey, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - BP142: Allen, Zachariah, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - BP143: Crosby, Thomas Jr., [undated] (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - BP144: Archibald, Raymond Clare, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - BP145: Barbour, Clarence Augustus, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - BP146: Goddard, Josiah, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - BP147: Goddard, Eliza Ann Abbott, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - BP148: Corthell, Elmer Lawrence, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - BP149: Metcalf, Jesse Houghton, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - BP150: Wriston, Henry Merritt, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - BP151: Sharpe, Henry Dexter, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - BP152: Cooke, Nicholas, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - BP153: Morriss, Margaret Shove, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - BP154: Wayland, Francis, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - BP155: Ide, Jacob, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - BP156 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - BP157: Wheaton, Henry, 2009-2015 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - BP158: Delabarre, Edmund Burke, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - BP159: Brown, John Nicholas, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - BP160: Kraus, Charles August, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - BP161: Allen, Arthur Moulton, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - BP162: Falk, Lester Leopold, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - BP163: Hunter, Walter Samuel, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - BP164: Unidentified, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - BP165: Angell, Joseph K., [undated] (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - BP166: Unidentified, 1973-1989 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - BP167: Whipple, Abraham, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - BP168: Lewis, Nancy Duke, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - BP169: D'Wolf, John, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - BP170: Bigelow, Bruce MacMillan, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - BP171: Brown, Benjamin Williams, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - BP172: Arnold, Samuel Tomlinson, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - BP173: Wilson, James Walter, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - BP174: Sharpe, Henry Dexter, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - BP175: Sharpe, Mary Elizabeth (Evans), [undated] (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - BP176: Manning, Henry Parker, [undated] (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - BP177: Sears, Loren O, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - BP178: Rockefeller, John D., Jr., [undated] (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - BP179: Tanner, Harold Brooks, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - BP180: Paine, Royal, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - BP181: Mitchell, Robert McBurney, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - BP182: Wriston, Henry Merritt, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - BP183: Keeney, Barnaby Conrad, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - BP184: Bigelow, Bruce MacMillan, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - BP185: Metcalf, Jesse Houghton, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - BP186: Slade, William Adams, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - BP187: Parsons, Usher, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - BP188: Parsons, Usher, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - BP189: Burnside, Ambrose Everett, 1938-2016 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - BP190: Appleget, Thomas Baird, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - BP191: Brown James, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - BP192: Philip IV, King of Spain, 1957-2015 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - BP193:Parsons, Usher, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - BP194: Sackville, Lord, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - BP195: Sackville, Lady, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - BP196: Corliss, George Henry, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - BP197: Hay, John, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - BP198: Ritchie, G.W.H., [undated] (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - BP199: Steere, Arnold, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - BP200: Faunce, William Herbert Perry, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - BP201: Keeney, Barnaby Conrad, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - BP202: Hoyt, David Webster, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - BP203: Robinson, Ezekiel Gilman, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - BP204: Goddard, William, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - BP205: Goddard, Mary Jenckes, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - BP206: Wayland, Francis, 1967-1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - BP207: Pierrel, Rosemary, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - BP208: Hoffman, William Henry, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - BP209: Heffner, Ray Lorenzo, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - BP210: Nicholson, Samuel Mowry, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - BP211: Nicholson, Mary Jewett Coe, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - BP212: Wayland, Sarah, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - BP213: Brown, Janice Oakley Van De Water, 1971-1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - BP214: Jones, Leslie Allen, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - BP215: Hay, John, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - BP216: Princesse de Lamballe, 1920-2010 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - BP217: Unidentified Portrait of a Man, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - BP218: Unidentified Portrait of a Man, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - BP219: Unidentified Portrait of a Man, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - BP220: Damon, Foster S., [undated] (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - BP221: Wheelwright, John Brooks, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Unlocated: Angell, Joseph Kinnecutt, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Unlocated: Colby, Gardner, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Unlocated: Estcourt, Thomas, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Unlocated: Hopkins, Esek, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Unlocated: Martin, Philip, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Unlocated: Tallmadge, James, [undated] (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Tolman, Stacy, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Portraits, 1857-2005 (Box 8, Folder 53)